export default  [
    {
        "category": "React",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "hard",
        "question": "React is mainly used for building ___.",
        "correct_answer": "User interface",
          "incorrect_answers": [
            "Database",
            "Connectivity",
            "Design Platform"
          ]
      },
      {
        "category": "React",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "hard",
        "question": "What is React?",
        "correct_answer": "React is an open-source front-end JavaScript library",
          "incorrect_answers": [
            "React is an open-source front-end Golang library",
            "React is an open-source front-end Java library",
            "React is an open-source front-end PHP library"
          ]
      },
      {
        "category": "React",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "hard",
        "question": "What is JSX?",
        "correct_answer": "JSX is a XML-like syntax extension to ECMAScript",
          "incorrect_answers": [
            "JSX does not exists",
            "JSX is a JSON-like syntax extension to ECMAScript",
            "JSX is a XML-like syntax extension to Java"
          ]
      },
      {
        "category": "React",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "hard",
        "question": "How to create components in React?",
        "correct_answer": "Function and Class Components",
          "incorrect_answers": [
            "Function and Object Components",
            "Object and Class Components",
            "Function and Interface Components"
          ]
      },
      {
        "category": "React",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "hard",
        "question": "What is the concept state in React?",
        "correct_answer": "State of a component is an object that holds some information that may change over the lifetime of the component.",
          "incorrect_answers": [
            "State is the response code of a HTTP request.",
            "State is used for authentication.",
            "State doesn't exists in React."
          ]
      },
      {
        "category": "React",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "hard",
        "question": "What is the Virtual DOM?",
        "correct_answer": "The Virtual DOM is a concept implemented by libraries in JavaScript on top of browser APIs.",
          "incorrect_answers": [
            "The Virtual DOM does not exists.",
            "The Virtual DOM is a programming language to write browsers.",
            "The Virtual DOM is a virtual machine that is running your React code."
          ]
      },
      {
        "category": "React",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "hard",
        "question": "What is React Fiber?",
        "correct_answer": "Fiber is the new reconciliation engine or reimplementation of core algorithm in React v16",
          "incorrect_answers": [
            "Fiber is a networking JavaScript library.",
            "React Fiber is the newest version of React.",
            "It's a React spinoff"
          ]
      },
      {
        "category": "React",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "hard",
        "question": "What are fragments?",
        "correct_answer": "It's a common pattern in React which is used for a component to return multiple elements",
          "incorrect_answers": [
            "It's a way to make your React application more modular.",
            "Fragmenting your code in smaller pieces.",
            "A coding pattern for JavaScript development"
          ]
      },
      {
        "category": "React",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "hard",
        "question": "What are hooks?",
        "correct_answer": "Hooks is a function that lets you use state and other React features without writing a class.",
          "incorrect_answers": [
            "Hooks are webhook for React.",
            "They are connecting multiple functions and execute them asynchonously.",
            "Hooks are a legacy component from React to leverage the concept of webhooks in JavaScript."
          ]
      },
      {
        "category": "React",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "hard",
        "question": "Playwright supports following rendering engines.",
        "correct_answer": "All of them",
          "incorrect_answers": [
            "Chromium",
            "WebKit",
            "Firefox"
          ]
      },
      {
        "category": "PowerBI",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "hard",
        "question": "What is the device posture API used for?",
        "correct_answer": "To detect foldable devices screens angle",
          "incorrect_answers": [
            "To monitor user's posture to avoid back pain",
            "To detect dropping devices to flush caches and prevent data loss",
            "To detect if front or back camera is used"
          ]
      },
      {
        "category": "PowerBI",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "hard",
        "question": "What was the first mainstream foldable multi-screen device?",
        "correct_answer": "Nintendo Game & Watch",
          "incorrect_answers": [
            "Surface Duo",
            "Galaxy Fold",
            "LG G8X ThinQ"
          ]
      },
      {
        "category": "PowerBI",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "hard",
        "question": "What CSS feature is used to create responsive designs?",
        "correct_answer": "Media queries",
          "incorrect_answers": [
            "Selectors",
            "Flex box",
            "Sass"
          ]
      },
      {
        "category": "PowerBI",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "hard",
        "question": "What can be used to reduce data access latency in a distributed app?",
        "correct_answer": "Cache",
          "incorrect_answers": [
            "Database",
            "Queue",
            "An Intel Pentium processor"
          ]
      },
      {
        "category": "PowerBI",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "hard",
        "question": "Which one(s) of these Azure solutions can you use to deploy containers?",
        "correct_answer": "All the answers",
          "incorrect_answers": [
            "Azure Container Instances",
            "Azure Kubernetes Service",
            "Azure Container Apps"
          ]
      },

      {
        "category": "React",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "hard",
        "question": "Playwright enables reliable _____ for modern web apps",
        "correct_answer": "end-to-end testing",
          "incorrect_answers": [
            "performance testing",
            "quality testing",
            "continious integration"
          ]
      },
      {
        "category": "React",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "hard",
        "question": "Playwright Test supports TypeScript out of the box.",
        "correct_answer": "Yes",
          "incorrect_answers": [
            "No",
            "It's on the roadmap"
          ]
      },
      {
        "category": "React",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "hard",
        "question": "You can hook up Playwright to following JavaScript test runner.",
        "correct_answer": "Jest / Jasmine, Mocha, Vitest",
          "incorrect_answers": [
            "Jest / Jasmine, Mocha",
            "Mocha, Vitest",
            "Mocha, Vitest, Jenkins"
          ]
      },
      {
        "category": "React",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "hard",
        "question": "What is the GUI tool that lets you explore recorded Playwright traces of your tests?",
        "correct_answer": "Playwright Trace Viewer",
          "incorrect_answers": [
            "Playwright Tracer",
            "Playwright Viewer ",
            "Playwright GUI"
          ]
      },
      {
        "category": "React",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "hard",
        "question": "What is following code doing? -> `npx playwright test`",
        "correct_answer": "Runs all my tests",
          "incorrect_answers": [
            "Creates a new test",
            "Opens the GUI to show my tests",
            "Doesn't do anything"
          ]
      },
      {
        "category": "React",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "hard",
        "question": "Which of the following companies has developed and designed TypeScript?",
        "correct_answer": "Microsoft",
          "incorrect_answers": [
            "Amazon",
            "Google",
            "Facebook"
          ]
      },
      {
        "category": "React",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "hard",
        "question": "What is the typing principle of typescript?",
        "correct_answer": "Duck",
          "incorrect_answers": [
            "All of the above",
            "Dynamic",
            "Gradual"
          ]
      },
      {
        "category": "React",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "hard",
        "question": "Which of the computer programming languages below has influenced the creation of typescript?",
        "correct_answer": "All of the above",
          "incorrect_answers": [
            "JavaScript",
            "Java",
            "C#"
          ]
      },
      {
        "category": "React",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "hard",
        "question": "All are backported features of TypeScript, exceptâ€¦.",
        "correct_answer": "Methods",
          "incorrect_answers": [
            "Modules",
            "Classes",
            "Arrows"
          ]
      },
      {
        "category": "React",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "hard",
        "question": "The advantages of Typescript are...",
        "correct_answer": "All of the above.",
          "incorrect_answers": [
            "It assists in code structuring.",
            "It applies class -based object oriented programming.",
            "It introduces coding guidelines."
          ]
      },
      {
        "category": "React",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "hard",
        "question": "What variable scopes are available in TypeScript?",
        "correct_answer": "All of the above.",
          "incorrect_answers": [
            "Global Scope",
            "Local Scope",
            "Class Scope"
          ]
      },
      {
        "category": "React",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "hard",
        "question": "A typescript may be installed or managed through...",
        "correct_answer": "Nmp",
          "incorrect_answers": [
            "Void",
            "Space",
            "Tag"
          ]
      },
      {
        "category": "React",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "hard",
        "question": "Which statements below are true about JSX modes?",
        "correct_answer": "The preserve mode keeps the JSX as part of the output to be further consumed by another transform step.",
          "incorrect_answers": [
            "The react mode will emit React.addElement.",
            "The preserve, react, and react native modes donâ€™t affect the emit stage - type checking is affected.",
            "The output of react mode has a .jsx file extension."
          ]
      },
      {
        "category": "React",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "hard",
        "question": "What does Typescript use for anonymous functions?",
        "correct_answer": "\"arrow\" syntax",
          "incorrect_answers": [
            "\"dot\" syntax",
            "\"dollar\" syntax",
            "None of the above"
          ]
      },
      {
        "category": "PowerBI",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "hard",
        "question": "Can you get started for free with Microsoft Azure?",
        "correct_answer": "Yes, everyone can with the free tier",
          "incorrect_answers": [
            "No you can't",
            "Only if you are a student",
            "Yes if you are a .NET developer"
          ]
      },
      {
        "category": "React",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "hard",
        "question": "Azure App Service is a service for hosting ___.â€‹",
        "correct_answer": "web applications (JavaScript, NodeJS, Java, Mobile, and more).â€‹",
          "incorrect_answers": [
            "web applications written in .NET",
            "mobile Apps only",
            "high processing workloads"
          ]
      },
      {
        "category": "PowerBI",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "hard",
        "question": "What is a static Web app in Azure?",
        "correct_answer": "Azure Static Web Apps is a service that automatically builds and deploys full stack web apps to Azure from a code repository.",
          "incorrect_answers": [
            "Azure Static Web Apps are used for non-JavaScript applications",
            "Azure Static Web Apps is used solely for server-side apps",
            "Azure Static Web apps doesn't exists, Azure Web Apps does."
          ]
      },
      {
        "category": "PowerBI",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "hard",
        "question": "Is Azure static Web apps free?",
        "correct_answer": "It's available through two different plans, Free and Standard",
          "incorrect_answers": [
            "No, it's paid.",
            "Yes, but only for students.",
            "Yes with a coupon code."
          ]
      },
      {
        "category": "PowerBI",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "hard",
        "question": "What is Github Artifacts?",
        "correct_answer": "A way to store data produced by a workflow",
          "incorrect_answers": [
            "A cloud storage solution from Github",
            "A place to store source code",
            "A change request to your code base"
          ]
      },
      {
        "category": "PowerBI",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "hard",
        "question": "Which Microsoft product helps developers starting a new project quickly and efficiently?",
        "correct_answer": "Azure Dev Box",
          "incorrect_answers": [
            "Azure Virtual Desktop",
            "Windows 365",
            "Visual Workshop"
          ]
      },
      {
        "category": "PowerBI",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "hard",
        "question": "What is an octopus merge?",
        "correct_answer": "It takes two or more branches and merge them in a single branch",
          "incorrect_answers": [
            "It stages several commits and merges them at once",
            "It's a type of octopus living in the atlantic ocean",
            "It's a merge done with Git Kraken"
          ]
      },
      {
        "category": "PowerBI",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "hard",
        "question": "What is a protected branch in Github?",
        "correct_answer": "A branch which you must meet certain standards to be able to commit to it",
          "incorrect_answers": [
            "A secured branch which only accepts perfect code",
            "A hidden branch, and only available for specific users or groups",
            "A branch used to work on security features"
          ]
      },
      {
        "category": "PowerBI",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "hard",
        "question": "What was Github copilot trained on?",
        "correct_answer": "Public GitHub repositories",
          "incorrect_answers": [
            "Private GitHub repositories",
            "Windows repository",
            "Stackoverflow"
          ]
      },
  ]